A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Room 5600, Rockefeller family office, Series 2 FA455
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Nelson A. Rockefeller Photographs, Room 5600, Rockefeller family office, 1920-1979; 2; 32.73 Cubic Feet
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Photographs, 1909-1979; 18.33 Cubic Feet 39 legal document boxes.
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Government Service - International Development Advisory Board (IDAB)
      - International Development Advisory Board (Box 11, Folder 166)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Government Service, Under Secretary of Department of Health, Education and Welfare
      - Under Secretary of Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1953-1954; (5) (Box 11, Folder 167)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Government Service, Special Assistant to the President for Foreign Affairs
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Political- Special Assistant to the President for Foreign Affairs, 1954-1955; (5) (Box 11, Folder 168)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Gubernatorial, Appearances
      - Mr. and Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller meet Mr. and Mrs. Harriman, Executive Mansion, 1958; (7) (Box 12, Folder 169)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Inauguration - Albany, 1958; (35) (Box 12, Folder 170)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Inauguration (Box 12, Folder 171)
      - Sleepy Hollow Restorations: Historic Hudson Valley, Nelson A. Rockefeller and Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller, circa 1959; (11) (Box 12, Folder 172)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Loyalty Day Parade, Mayor Wagner, Spelman, 1959; (2) (Box 12, Folder 173)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Varied, 1959; (10 photos, 73 contact sheet images) (Box 12, Folder 174)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Legal Bills Signing, 1959 April; (1) (Box 12, Folder 175)
      - Puerto Rican Governor's conference, 1959 August; (2) (Box 12, Folder 176)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Various Scenes, 1961-1970; (34 photos, 8 contact sheet with 85 images, 4 slides) (Box 12, Folder 177)
      - Luncheon for U. Thant, 1962 December 27; (9) (Box 12, Folder 178)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Garden City, Long Island with MFR and others, 1963 or 1964; (24) (Box 12, Folder 179)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller and MFR with Bust of Columbus and John Lomenzo, circa 1965 October; (5) (Box 12, Folder 180)
      - Humanitarian Award, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 181)
      - Fordham Law Luncheon, 1966 February 19; (18) (Box 12, Folder 182)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller, MFR, Robert Kennedy, 1966 February 25; (1) (Box 12, Folder 183)
      - Annual Debutante Cotillion, 1966 March 25; (2) (Box 12, Folder 184)
      - Ogdensburg, NY, 1966 April 20 (Box 12, Folder 185)
      - Turbine Powered Rail Passenger Car - LIRR, 1966 September 12; (1) (Box 12, Folder 186)
      - Amun-Israel Housing Corp. Luncheon, 1966 October 2; (3) (Box 12, Folder 187)
      - SUNY Binghamton, 1967; (1) (Box 12, Folder 188)
      - Water Pollution Control Workshop, Buffalo, NY, 1967 January 27; (1) (Box 12, Folder 189)
      - "Most Scenic New Highway" Award, Albany, 1967 March 7; (9) (Box 12, Folder 190)
      - West Point Cadets, Albany, 1967 March 29; (2) (Box 12, Folder 191)
      - Israel Histadrut Campaign, 1967 April 29; (3) (Box 12, Folder 192)
      - Downstate Medical Center, 1967 May 5; (3) (Box 12, Folder 193)
      - Committee of Intergovernmental Relations, Washington DC, 1967 July 21; (2) (Box 12, Folder 194)
      - National Governor's Conference, 1967 October; (1) (Box 12, Folder 195)
      - 30th Anniversary at 1000 Island Bridge Project, 1968 June 4; (9) (Box 12, Folder 196)
      - Airport with Mr. and Mrs. George Hinman, 1968 November 6; (2) (Box 12, Folder 197)
      - NYS. Power Authority, Niagara Falls, NY, 1969 August 2; (20) (Box 13, Folder 198)
      - 63 rd St. Tunnel Dedication Ceremony, circa 1970; (1) (Box 13, Folder 199)
      - Republican State Nominating Meeting, Rochester, NY, 1970 April 6-7; (8) (Box 13, Folder 200)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller, J Edgar Hoover, 1971 July 28; (1) (Box 13, Folder 201)
      - White House Fellows, 1973 June 1; 1 contact sheet with 9 images (Box 13, Folder 202)
      - Fortune Magazine, 1973 June 1; 1 contact sheet with 23 images (Box 13, Folder 203)
      - Wagner Commission, 1973 June 12; 1 contact sheet with 6 images (Box 13, Folder 204)
      - United Service Bill Signing & Swearing in Santiago Grovi, 1973 June 12; (9 contact sheets with 106 images) (Box 13, Folder 205)
      - Labor Reception, 1973 June 12; (2 contact sheets with 23 images) (Box 13, Folder 206)
      - Republican State Committee Dinner, 1973 June 14; (3 contact sheets with 55 images) (Box 13, Folder 207)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Anderson, 1973 June 14; 1 contact sheet with 11 images (Box 13, Folder 208)
      - Moshacher Swearing in, 1973 August 7; 2 contact sheets with 60 images (Box 13, Folder 209)
      - Swearing In 16 Judges, 1973 September 10; 4 contact sheets with 60 images (Box 13, Folder 210)
      - Bridge and Tunnel Officers, 1973 September 18; 2 contact sheets with 19 images (Box 13, Folder 211)
      - Japanese Press, 1973 September 18; 2 contact sheets with 15 images (Box 13, Folder 212)
      - Albany Cabinet Meeting, 1973 October 16; 5 contact sheets with 91 images (Box 13, Folder 213)
      - Skylab Crew, Lunar Sample, 1973 October 24; 1 contact sheet with 9 images (Box 13, Folder 214)
      - White House Fellows, 1973 October 30; 1 contact sheet with 17 images (Box 13, Folder 215)
      - Howard Shapiro Swearing In, 1973 November 7; 2 contact sheets with 23 images (Box 13, Folder 216)
      - Lee Goodwin Swearing In, 1973 November 12; (1 photo, 1 contact sheet with 12 images) (Box 13, Folder 217)
      - Jobs for Veterans Award to Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1973 November 28; 1 contact sheet, 12 images (Box 13, Folder 218)
      - Commission on Critical Choices Dinner, 1973 December 3; (13 photos, 1 contact sheet with 18 images) (Box 13, Folder 219)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Resignation, 1973 December 11 (Box 13, Folder 220)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller / Duryea - Gubernatorial, 1973; (1) (Box 13, Folder 221)
      - Educational and Cultural Trust Fund, NY, (40) (Box 13, Folder 222)
      - NYS. AFL-CIO 4th Annual Convention, (2) (Box 13, Folder 223)
      - Camp Smith, Peekskill, NY, (5) (Box 13, Folder 224)
      - Apollo 8 Astronauts banquet, (10) (Box 13, Folder 225)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller visits Adirondacks, (11) (Box 13, Folder 226)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller with State Commerce Commissioner McHugh, (1) (Box 13, Folder 227)
      - Greeting Ronald and Nancy Regan, (3) (Box 13, Folder 228)
      - West Point Cadets, Albany, (3) (Box 13, Folder 229)
      - Intergovernmental Relations Committee, (4) (Box 13, Folder 230)
      - Israel Histadrut Campaign, (1) (Box 13, Folder 231)
      - Seal of the State of New York, (1); negative only (Box 13, Folder 232)
      - NAR, Mrs. NAR, ILGWU, AFL-CIO (Box 13, Folder 233)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial, Campaigns
      - Sammy Schulman Photographs, 1958 Campaign. Master Shots., [R1-R64] (Box 14, Folder 234)
      - Duplicates of Sammy Schulman Nelson A. Rockefeller and Mary opening headquarters (4 August), 1958; (12) (Box 15, Folder 235)
      - Republican Rally Dinner, 1958; (12 photos, 1 negative) (Box 14, Folder 236)
      - Mr. and Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Gene Oliver / with Elaine Broadbent and N.D. Stefano, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 237)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller tours- Cooperstown, Hotel Roosevelt, Harlem, Middletown, Albany, Staten Island, (33) (Box 14, Folder 238)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Pitching - Red Wing Stadium, 1958 August; (1) (Box 14, Folder 239)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller 1958 Campaign Photographs, (105 photos, 4 engraving plates, 2 mats) (Box 15, Folder 240)
      - World Wide Contact Prints - 1958 Nelson A. Rockefeller Campaign, (62 contact sheets with 604 images) (Box 15, Folder 241)
      - World Wide Contact Prints - Nelson A. Rockefeller Campaign, (99 contact sheets with 821 images) (Box 15, Folder 242)
      - Watertown Times, 1958 September 3 (Box 16, Folder 243)
      - Primary Headquarters, Washington DC, 1960; (7) (Box 16, Folder 244)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Campaigns for Nixon, 1960; (2) (Box 16, Folder 245)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Campaigning, 1962?; (11) (Box 16, Folder 246)
      - New Hampshire Primary, 1964; (42 contact sheets with 477 images, 30 photos, 12 contact images with negatives, 19 negatives) (Box 16, Folder 247)
      - Oregon Primary, 1964; (10) (Box 16, Folder 248)
      - Vermont Campaign, 1964; (42) (Box 16, Folder 249)
      - California's Primary, 1964; (158) (Box 16, Folder 250)
      - California's Primary, 1964; (188) (Box 17, Folder 251)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller NY Headquarters, 1964; (1) (Box 17, Folder 252)
      - Campaign Miscellaneous, Nelson A. Rockefeller Family at NYS. Republican Convention, 1966; (1) (Box 17, Folder 253)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller and Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller vote at Tarrytown, 1966 November 8; (1) (Box 17, Folder 254)
      - Campaign, 1968 (Montana Trip and Hawaii), (3) (Box 17, Folder 255)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Campaign, 1968 (with Governor James Rhodes and Congressman William Minshall) Rockefeller for President, Campaign swing through Ohio, 1968 July 18; (7) (Box 17, Folder 256)
      - Coney Island, 1970; (6) (Box 17, Folder 257)
      - Long Beach, 1970; (8) (Box 17, Folder 258)
      - Campaign 72 (Presidential), 1972; (9 contact sheets with 89 images) (Box 17, Folder 259)
      - South Mall, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 259A)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial. Albums
      - Volume II (Album), 1959 (Box 17, Folder 260)
      - Volume III (Album), 1959 (Box 17, Folder 261)
      - Volume IV (Album), 1959 (Box 18, Folder 262)
      - Volume I (Album), 1960 (Box 18, Folder 263)
      - Volume II (Album), 1960 February 22-March 15 (Box 18, Folder 264)
      - Volume III (Album), 1960 March 15-April 14 (Box 18, Folder 265)
      - Volume IV (Album), 1960 April 15-December 14 (Box 18, Folder 266)
      - Volume I (Album), 1961 January 1-February 20 (Box 18, Folder 267)
      - Volume II (Album), 1961 February 20-March 21 (Box 19, Folder 268)
      - Volume III (Album), 1961 March 22-May 29 (Box 19, Folder 269)
      - Volume IV (Album), 1961 June 12-December 26 (Box 19, Folder 270)
      - Governor "Swearing In" NY City, Albany, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 271)
      - General (Album), 1959-1963 (Box 19, Folder 272)
      - 4-H Club Work in New York State (Album), 1960 March (Box 19, Folder 273)
      - Politics and Appearances (Album), 1942 (Box 19, Folder 274)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice-Presidential
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Sworn In, 1974; (1) (Box 20, Folder 275)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Miscellaneous Photos, 1974-1975; (4) (Box 20, Folder 276)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Photos, Miscellaneous, 1976; (12) (Box 20, Folder 277)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Photos, Miscellaneous, undated; (34) (Box 20, Folder 278)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Photos, Miscellaneous, 1974; (33) (Box 20, Folder 279)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Photos, Miscellaneous, 1975; (45) (Box 20, Folder 280)
      - 1974 August 20, (9) (Box 20, Folder 281)
      - 1974 August 22, (4) (Box 20, Folder 282)
      - 1974 August 24, (1) (Box 20, Folder 283)
      - 1974 August 28, (16) (Box 20, Folder 284)
      - Hearings, 1974 December; (5) (Box 20, Folder 285)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Vice-Presidential Inauguration, 1974 December 19; (37) (Box 20, Folder 286)
      - Inauguration Party, 1974 December 19; (10) (Box 20, Folder 287)
      - 1974 December 21, (4) (Box 20, Folder 288)
      - 1975 January 3, (1) (Box 20, Folder 289)
      - 1975 January 8, (2) (Box 20, Folder 290)
      - 1975 January 10, (2) (Box 20, Folder 291)
      - 1975 January 13 (Box 20, Folder 292)
      - 1975 January 13 (Box 20, Folder 293)
      - 1975 January 14, (12) (Box 20, Folder 294)
      - 1975 January 15, (3) (Box 20, Folder 295)
      - 1975 January 16, (10) (Box 20, Folder 296)
      - 1975 January 17, (2) (Box 20, Folder 297)
      - 1975 January 22, (1) (Box 20, Folder 298)
      - 1975 January 23, (8) (Box 20, Folder 299)
      - 1975 January 24, (1) (Box 20, Folder 300)
      - 1975 January 27, (2) (Box 20, Folder 301)
      - 1975 January 28, (7) (Box 20, Folder 302)
      - 1975 January 29, (5) (Box 20, Folder 303)
      - 1975 January 30, (2) (Box 20, Folder 304)
      - 1975 January 31, (1) (Box 20, Folder 305)
      - 1975 February 3, (1) (Box 20, Folder 306)
      - 1975 February 13, (4) (Box 20, Folder 307)
      - 1975 February 14, (2) (Box 20, Folder 308)
      - 1975 February 17, (2) (Box 20, Folder 309)
      - 1975 February 18, (4) (Box 20, Folder 310)
      - 1975 February 20, (3) (Box 20, Folder 311)
      - 1975 March 4, (1) (Box 21, Folder 312)
      - 1975 March 27, (1) (Box 21, Folder 313)
      - 1975 April 10 (Box 21, Folder 314)
      - 1975 April 23, (15) (Box 21, Folder 315)
      - 1975 May 1, (16) (Box 21, Folder 316)
      - 1975 May 2, (8) (Box 21, Folder 317)
      - 1975 May 7, (12) (Box 21, Folder 318)
      - 1975 May 8, (2) (Box 21, Folder 319)
      - 1975 May 9, (3) (Box 21, Folder 320)
      - 1975 May 28, (3) (Box 21, Folder 321)
      - 1975 May 29, (2) (Box 21, Folder 322)
      - 1975 June 3, (2) (Box 21, Folder 323)
      - 1975 June 5, (5) (Box 21, Folder 324)
      - 1975 June 11, (4) (Box 21, Folder 325)
      - 1975 June 17, (2) (Box 21, Folder 326)
      - Prime Minister Harold Wilson, London, 1975 July 2; (1),(10); July 2, 1975 (1) July 9, 1975 (10) (Box 21, Folder 327)
      - 1975 July 9 (Box 21, Folder 328)
      - Tukeo Miki Prime Minister of Japan, 1975 August; (8) (Box 21, Folder 329)
      - United Negro College Fund Drive, 1975 October 24; (12) (Box 21, Folder 330)
      - Kennedy Center, 1976 January 25; (1) (Box 21, Folder 331)
      - Reenactment of Inauguration of George Washington, 1976 April 30; (3) (Box 21, Folder 332)
      - Queen Margrethe II and Prince Henrik of Denmark, 1976 May 11; (2) (Box 21, Folder 333)
      - White House Meeting regarding Italian Earthquake, 1976 May 17; (3) (Box 21, Folder 334)
      - President Valry Giscard d'Estaing of France, 1976 May 18 or 19; (1) (Box 21, Folder 335)
      - Lyndon Baines Johnson Memorial Grove on the Potomac Dedication, (31) (Box 21, Folder 336)
      - U.S. Air Force Academy, 1976 June; (4) (Box 21, Folder 337)
      - 1976 July 1, (4) (Box 21, Folder 338)
      - Marrine Barracks Evening Parade in Honor of Vice President, 1976 July 2; (9) (Box 21, Folder 339)
      - Queen Elizabeth, 1976 July 8; (1) (Box 21, Folder 340)
      - Dinner for Queen Elizabeth, 1976 July 9; (4) (Box 21, Folder 341)
      - Dinner for Prime Minister of Australia, 1976 July 28; (1) (Box 21, Folder 342)
      - Dinner given by President of Finland, 1976 August 4; (2) (Box 21, Folder 343)
      - V.P. NYS. Republican Campaign Tour, 1976 September 16; (8) (Box 21, Folder 344)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Campaigning, 1976; (35) (Box 21, Folder 345)
      - French Ambassador, Kosciuko-Morizet, 1977 January 9; (1) (Box 21, Folder 346)
      - National Geographic Society Dinner, circa 1977; (4) (Box 21, Folder 347)
      - Photographs - Nelson A. Rockefeller presenting Service Awards, (23) (Box 21, Folder 348)
      - Federal Handicapped of the Year Award, 1977; (20) photos in notebook (Box 21, Folder 349)
      - Vice Presidential Office Seal, (1) (Box 21, Folder 350)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Homes - Bar Harbor, Maine
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller - birthplace - Weymouth Lane - Bar Harbor, Maine, 1948; (6) (Box 22, Folder 351)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Homes - Seal Harbor, Maine
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Homes - Seal Harbor, Maine (photos of grounds), 1964; (8) (Box 22, Folder 352)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Home (Seal Harbor) - Anchorage, (14) (Box 22, Folder 353)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Homes - Governor's Mansion, Albany, New York
      - Executive Mansion - Flower Gardens, and photos of Mall, (36) (Box 22, Folder 354)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Homes - Governor's Mansion, Albany, (1 photo, 56 slides) (Box 22, Folder 355)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Homes - Hawes House, Pocantico Hills, New York
      - Hawes House - Pocantico Hills, NY, (25) (Box 22, Folder 356)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Homes - Washington DC
      - 2500 Foxhall Rd., Washington, DC, 1974; (2) (Box 22, Folder 357)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Homes - Japanese House, Pocantico Hills, NY
      - Construction of Japanese House, (19) (Box 22, Folder 358)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Homes - Monte Sacro, Venezuela
      - Photos of "House on the Hill" Chirgua, (12) (Box 22, Folder 359)
      - Residence - "Monte Sacro", Valencia Venezuela, (84 photos, 13 negatives) (Box 22, Folder 360)
      - Monte Sacro Farm, Venezuela, color shots by Peter K Ogden, 1958 November; (36) (Box 22, Folder 361)
      - Monte Sacro, 1968; (45) (Box 23, Folder 362)
      - Monte Sacro, 1974; (11 contact sheets with 212 images and 192 negatives) (Box 23, Folder 363)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Personal - Childhood
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Personal - Childhood (Box 23, Folder 364)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Personal - Childhood - Pre-College - Family Scenes, 1909-1918 (Box 23, Folder 365)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Personal - College
      - Dartmouth College Class of ' 30 Group Portrait, 1930; (1) (Box 23, Folder 366)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Executive Committee of Senior Class, Dartmouth, 1930; (1) (Box 23, Folder 367)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Dartmouth Photos, (8 photos, 3 negatives) (Box 23, Folder 368)
      - Photos Taken by Nelson A. Rockefeller of a Dartmouth Theater Production, 1929; (8) (Box 23, Folder 369)
      - Dartmouth, 1968; (5) (Box 23, Folder 370)
      - Dartmouth (Album) - Reunion, 1974 June 18 (Box 23, Folder 371)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Personal - Miscellaneous
      - Personal Photographs, 1920-1948; (28) (Box 24, Folder 372)
      - Table given to President Eisenhower by Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1955; (1) (Box 24, Folder 373)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Captioned photos of the activities of Nelson A. Rockefeller and family in New York, etc-for Javits TV show, 1958 October; (13) (Box 24, Folder 374)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller on Horseback - Monte Sacro, 1958; (1) (Box 24, Folder 375)
      - LOOK Magazine photos of farm, family, politics, received July 6, 1960 duplicates, negatives, 1960 July 6; (14) (Box 24, Folder 376)
      - Sports - Sailing - with sons Rodman and Steven, Maine, 1958; (7) (Box 24, Folder 377)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Photos of Nelson A. Rockefeller's hands, 1961; (17) (Box 24, Folder 378)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Sports - Skiing, undated; (1) (Box 24, Folder 379)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Golfing - Hawaii, 1961 June 25; (1) (Box 24, Folder 380)
      - Michael Rockefeller, Metropolitan Museum Dedication, 1969; (11) (Box 24, Folder 381)
      - Party for Kissinger, 1974 June 22; (91) (Box 24, Folder 382)
      - Nelson Jr. and Mark at Kissinger Party, 1974 June 22; (10) (Box 24, Folder 383)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller with Art (Album), late 1970s (Box 24, Folder 384)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Memorial Service, 1979 February 2; (34) (Box 24, Folder 385)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Philanthropy - American International Association for Economic and Social Development
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Political - American International Association for Economic and Social Development (AIA), 1946-1958; (9) (Box 24, Folder 386)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller in Venezuela (AIA), 1946-1948; (5) (Box 24, Folder 387)
      - PIIP Photos, 1964 June; (5) (Box 24, Folder 388)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Philanthropy - Victory Clothing Drive
      - Victory Clothing Drive, 1946; (53) (Box 24, Folder 389)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Politics and Appearances Pre 1958
      - F. LaGuardia, R. Rankin, Nelson A. Rockefeller negative, (1) (Box 25, Folder 390)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1947-1958; (7) (Box 25, Folder 391)
      - Great Island Conference, 1946; (6) (Box 25, Folder 392)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Museum of Modern Art opening - War Vets art and others, 1946; (1) (Box 25, Folder 393)
      - United Jewish Appeal Dinners, 1946; (2) (Box 25, Folder 394)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Wally Harrison, J.H. Whitney, others Museum Modern Art Dinners, 1947; (2) (Box 25, Folder 395)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller, National Conference of Christians and Jews - 20th Anniversary Dinner, 1948 November 18; (2) (Box 25, Folder 396)
      - National Conference of Christians and Jews 1949, Brotherhood Campaign, 1948 November-1949; (2) (Box 25, Folder 397)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Charles Wilson, Roger Strauss, Brotherhood Week Championship, 1949; (1) (Box 25, Folder 398)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Crowell-Collier Cornerstone Laying, 1949 March; (2) (Box 25, Folder 399)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Dr. Ralph Bunche, Mrs. Bunche, American Association for the United Nations, (3 photos, 1 negative) (Box 25, Folder 400)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Amun-Israeli Housing Corp Directors, 1950 March 9; (2) (Box 25, Folder 401)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Memorial Day Services - Pocantico Hills, 1956 May 30; (1) (Box 25, Folder 402)
      - National Urban League Dinner, 1956 November 14; (1) (Box 25, Folder 403)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller with Thomas E. Dewey, circa 1956; (1) (Box 25, Folder 404)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Pan American Union Dinner, (1) (Box 25, Folder 405)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller with Robert Frost, (1) (Box 25, Folder 406)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller greeting Mr. Wiznitzer of Diarioda Noticias Brazil, Nelson A. Rockefeller's office, (1) (Box 25, Folder 407)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller on Face the Nation (CBS) from Theodore Ayers, (3) (Box 25, Folder 408)
      - United Jewish Appeal - Person to Person Campaign, Nelson A. Rockefeller chairman, 1958; (5) (Box 25, Folder 409)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller speech in Spokane, WA, 1947; (2) (Box 25, Folder 410)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Board of Regents Bicentennial Convocation, (22 photos, slides, negatives), 1977 October 26 (Box 25, Folder 411)
      - (Album), 1943-1944 May (Box 25, Folder 412)
      - 1944 June-1945 (Box 25, Folder 413)
      - 1945 August-December (Box 25, Folder 414)
      - (Album), 1946-1947 (Box 26, Folder 415)
      - (Album), 1948-1954 (Box 26, Folder 416)
      - (Album), 1955-1958 (Box 26, Folder 417)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portraits
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portraits (Delar), 1928-1940; (13) (Box 27, Folder 418)
        Scope and Contents
        {1008.4/1 through 1008.4/13}
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portrait - Rockefeller Center photobacker and John D. Rockefeller, Sr. Pictures, 1930s; (18) (Box 27, Folder 419)
        {1008.4/14 through 1008.4/31}
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portrait - Harris & Ewing, 1945; (1) (Box 27, Folder 420)
        {1008.4/32}
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portrait - Harris & Ewing, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 421)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portrait - Harris & Ewing, circa 1945; (2) (Box 28, Folder 422)
        {1008.4/33 through 1008.4/34}
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portrait - mat and plate, (1) (Box 28, Folder 423)
        {1008.4/35}
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portrait - Gene Garrett, circa 1945; (5) (Box 28, Folder 424)
        {1008.4/36 through 1008.4/40}
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portrait - Cary B. Weilmer, Jr., 1950s; (3) (Box 28, Folder 425)
        {1008.4/41 through 1008.4/43}
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portrait - Camera Associates, 1950; (10) (Box 28, Folder 426)
        {1008.4/44 through 1008.4/53}
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portraits - Karsh (3 poses), 1945 (Box 28, Folder 427)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portrait - Town and Country Magazine, 1952; (2) (Box 28, Folder 428)
        {1008.4/54 through 1008.4/55}